http://www.roblon.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy – Roblon A/SPolicy for the processing and protection of personal data.The policy should help to ensure and document that Roblon A/S protects all personal data in accordance with the terms of The General Data Protection Regulation. The policy will also inform you about the processing and use of the registered personal data.1. Inventory of the processing of personal dataRoblon A/S processes the personal data of:EmployeesCustomersSuppliersWe have prepared a list of the processing of personal data. The inventory provides an overview of the processing of personal data that the company is responsible for. The data is mandatory for Roblon A/S to enter into employment, customer and supplier contracts.2. The purpose and the legal basis for the processingThe personal data are processed and collected relating to:Personnel management, including recruitment, hiring, termination and payment of wagesMaster data for customers, as well as marketing, orders and salesMaster data for vendors, as well as requisitions and purchaseWe only use the personal data for those purposes and we only collect the information adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in relation to safeguarding the purposes.3. Storage and deletion of personal dataRoblon A/S has implemented the following general guidelines for the storage and deletion of personal data:Personal data is kept in physical folders.Personal data is stored in IT systems and on server drives.Personal data is only stored for as long as it is necessary in relation to safeguarding the purposes.Personal data on employees are deleted at the latest five years after their employment has ended, and the personal data of any applicants will be deleted within six months. Read more here: The processing of Personal Data in the recruitment process at Roblon4. Data securityRoblon A/S has implemented the following security measures for the protection of personal data:Only employees who have a work-related need for access to the stored personal data, have access to it either physically or through it systems with access management.All computers have password, and the employees must not leave their passwords to others.Computers must have a firewall installed and antivirus software, is updated continuously.Physical folders are stored in a locked office or in locked cabinets.Personal data processed in the physical folders are deleted by shredding.Personal data to the external recipients is sent by secure mail.All employees must be instructed in handling and protection of personal data.5. DisclosurePersonal data about employees can be disclosed to public authorities, e.g. TAX and pension companies.6. Data processorsRoblon A/S only use data processors, which can guarantee that they will implement the appropriate technical and organizational security measures for the fulfilment of The General Data Protection Regulation requirements.7. RightsRoblon A/S is responsible for the rights of the data subject, including the right to access, withdrawal of consent, rectification and deletion, and Roblon A/S informs the data subject of the company's processing of personal data. Data subject has the right to complain to Datatilsynet. For further information go to: www.datatilsynet.dk8. Personal data breaches Roblon A/S documents it, if there were to be breaches of personal data. In the case of personal data breaches Datatilsynet will be notified according to applicable rules.Privacy policy and cookiesPolicy for the processing and protection of personal data collected on the website. In the following paragraphs it is explained how Roblon A/S will use the personal information, which you leave/or provide when you visit our website and use the various services on the website.1. Collection of personal informationYou will always be informed prior to the collection of personal information about you. The personal information we collect may include your name, your e-mail address and similar identifying information.2. The use of personal dataPersonal information is collected and used relating to:Signing up for newslettersMailing of other marketing material, including invitations to eventsStatisticsWe do note that the above-mentioned use shall only take place, if you have given your consent, unless the law allows that we may contact you without prior consent.Your information will be deleted when we no longer need to process them for the achievement of one or more of the above purposes. The information can be processed and retained for longer in anonymized form.3. CookiesWe use cookies on our site so that we can offer a user-friendly website with information that is relevant for you. A cookie is a small text file that is saved in your browser. This means that our website can recognize you when you visit the website again, and that we can keep statistics on how you and other users use the website. The first time you visit our website, you will get the information that we use cookies.We use cookies from Google Analytics.You have the option to block all cookies, delete existing cookies from your computer or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can get more information about how to avoid cookies by clicking on this link: minecookies.orgYou need to be aware that if you link to a 3. party website from Roblon A/S website, there may be new cookies that Roblon A/S do not have an influence on. In that case you need to read the website's cookie policy.4. SecurityWe have implemented security measures to ensure that our internal procedures meet our high security standards. We strive to protect the quality and integrity of your personal information in the best possible way.5. Access to your personal information, etc.You are at any time entitled to access the information which we process about you, however with certain legal exceptions. Furthermore, you have the right to object to the collection and the further processing of your personal information, just as you have the right to obtain rectification, deleting or blocking of your personal information.6. Links to other websites, etc.Our websites may contain links to other websites or integrated sites. We are not responsible for the content of other company’s websites or their practice in the relation to the collection of personal information. When you visit other websites, you are encouraged to read the privacy policy as well as other relevant policies.7. Change of information, etc.If you want us to update, change or delete personal information which we hold about you, wish to get access to the personal data processed about you, or do not wish to receive further communications from us, or if you have questions to the above guidelines, you can contact us on info@roblon.com. You can also write to us at the following address:Roblon A/SNordhavnsvej 1DK-9900 FrederikshavnThe site uses cookies to remember your settings and statistics. Information is shared with third parties. Read more hereCloseIndustriesBackIndustriesFiber Optic CablesWire & CablesOffshore Oil & GasEnergyOther industriesNewsBackNewsWIRE DüsseldorfExhibitionsAboutInvestorCareerContactDownloadsSearchIndustriesFiber Optic CablesWire & CablesOffshore Oil & GasEnergyOther industries
